export const quizData = [
  {
    category: 'quiz',
    questionText: 'Can tableau import data from Google Sheets?',
    questionNumber: 1,
    weekNumber: 1,
    answers: ['true', 'false'],
    correctAnswer: 'true',
  },
  {
    category: 'quiz',
    questionText:
      'Which visualization is best to show comparisons between two variables?',
    questionNumber: 2,
    weekNumber: 1,
    answers: ['line chart', 'scatter plot', 'heatmap', 'pie chart'],
    correctAnswer: 'scatter plot',
  },
  {
    category: 'quiz',
    questionText: 'Using a pie chart is best for what type of analysis?',
    questionNumber: 3,
    weekNumber: 1,
    answers: [
      'change over time',
      'proportion between categories',
      'aggregate of all categories',
      'geographic location of data',
    ],
    correctAnswer: 'proportion between categories',
  },
  {
    category: 'quiz',
    questionText: 'Which of the following is an example of categorical data?',
    questionNumber: 4,
    weekNumber: 1,
    answers: [
      'sum of student grades',
      'average GPA',
      'student club membership',
      'number of students who are ECON majors',
    ],
    correctAnswer: 'student club membership',
  },
  {
    category: 'quiz',
    questionText:
      'Which chart type is best for comparing categories of data as groups?',
    questionNumber: 5,
    weekNumber: 1,
    answers: ['multi-set column chart', 'pie chart', 'line chart', 'histogram'],
    correctAnswer: 'multi-set column chart',
  },
  {
    category: 'quiz',
    questionText: 'Can categorical data be visualized?',
    questionNumber: 6,
    weekNumber: 1,
    answers: ['true', 'false'],
    correctAnswer: 'true',
  },
  {
    category: 'quiz',
    questionText:
      'Can data visualization be used to tell two different stories with the same data?',
    questionNumber: 7,
    weekNumber: 1,
    answers: ['true', 'false'],
    correctAnswer: 'true',
  },
  {
    category: 'quiz',
    questionText: 'In Tableau, what type of data is described by measures?',
    questionNumber: 8,
    weekNumber: 1,
    answers: ['categorical data', 'numerical data', 'both', 'none'],
    correctAnswer: 'numerical data',
  },
  {
    category: 'quiz',
    questionText: 'Why do scholars and researcher visualize data?',
    questionNumber: 9,
    weekNumber: 1,
    answers: [
      'to create artwork',
      'to prove mathematical theorems',
      'to establish probably actions',
      'to find meaning in data',
    ],
    correctAnswer: 'to find meaning in data',
  },
  {
    category: 'quiz',
    questionText:
      'Which is not an important essential element of a data visualization?',
    questionNumber: 10,
    weekNumber: 1,
    answers: ['legend', 'title', 'company logo', 'scale'],
    correctAnswer: 'company logo',
  },
  {
    category: 'quiz',
    questionText:
      'Which of the following is not a major data type used in Tableau?',
    questionNumber: 1,
    weekNumber: 2,
    answers: ['string', 'temperature', 'number', 'boolean'],
    correctAnswer: 'temperature',
  },
  {
    category: 'quiz',
    questionText:
      'Which of the following is an example of a boolean data value?',
    questionNumber: 2,
    weekNumber: 2,
    answers: ['false', '12.53', 'mission accomplished', 'June 15, 2022'],
    correctAnswer: 'false',
  },
  {
    category: 'quiz',
    questionText:
      'Can Tableau understand city locations as a usable geographic data type?',
    questionNumber: 3,
    weekNumber: 2,
    answers: ['true', 'false'],
    correctAnswer: 'true',
  },
  {
    category: 'quiz',
    questionText:
      'What type of data is the following: Qatar Library 1st Floor?',
    questionNumber: 4,
    weekNumber: 2,
    answers: ['date and time', 'number', 'string', 'boolean'],
    correctAnswer: 'string',
  },
  {
    category: 'quiz',
    questionText: 'Which data is a good example of discrete data?',
    questionNumber: 5,
    weekNumber: 2,
    answers: [
      'prices of stocks since 1990',
      'winners of the world cup each year',
      'yearly academy award winners',
      'best film award by genre',
    ],
    correctAnswer: 'best film award by genre',
  },
  {
    category: 'quiz',
    questionText:
      'Can Tableau work with any data from Excel without the need for any data preparation?',
    questionNumber: 6,
    weekNumber: 2,
    answers: ['true', 'false'],
    correctAnswer: 'false',
  },
  {
    category: 'quiz',
    questionText:
      'What phrase best describes the optimal data formatting shape for use in Tableau?',
    questionNumber: 7,
    weekNumber: 2,
    answers: ['tall data', 'random data', 'wide data', 'condensed data'],
    correctAnswer: 'tall data',
  },
  {
    category: 'quiz',
    questionText: 'Which are examples of numeric data?',
    questionNumber: 8,
    weekNumber: 2,
    answers: ['93.23', '1000', '$29.99', 'all of the above'],
    correctAnswer: 'all of the above',
  },
  {
    category: 'quiz',
    questionText:
      'Is it possible to use categorical data on a bar chart in Tableau?',
    questionNumber: 9,
    weekNumber: 2,
    answers: ['true', 'false'],
    correctAnswer: 'true',
  },
  {
    category: 'quiz',
    questionText: 'Which file type cannot be imported into Tableau?',
    questionNumber: 10,
    weekNumber: 2,
    answers: ['excel workbook', 'CSV file', 'JPG file', 'tableau workbook'],
    correctAnswer: 'JPG file',
  },
  {
    category: 'quiz',
    questionText:
      'To create a scatter plot what is the minimum amount of information needed?',
    questionNumber: 1,
    weekNumber: 3,
    answers: [
      'two numerical data points',
      'one categorical and one numeric data point',
      'multiple categorical data points',
      'random data',
    ],
    correctAnswer: 'two numerical data points',
  },
  {
    category: 'quiz',
    questionText:
      'Can a scatter plot be used to establish correlation between two different data points?',
    questionNumber: 2,
    weekNumber: 3,
    answers: ['true', 'false'],
    correctAnswer: 'true',
  },
  {
    category: 'quiz',
    questionText:
      'What type of analytics is used for reviewing historical data?',
    questionNumber: 3,
    weekNumber: 3,
    answers: [
      'predictive analytics',
      'prescriptive analytics',
      'business analytics',
      'descriptive analytics',
    ],
    correctAnswer: 'descriptive analytics',
  },
  {
    category: 'quiz',
    questionText:
      'Which visualization in Tableau combines a data table with color to create a visualization?',
    questionNumber: 4,
    weekNumber: 3,
    answers: [
      'multi-set column chart',
      'highlight table',
      'pie chart',
      'scatter plot',
    ],
    correctAnswer: 'highlight table',
  },
  {
    category: 'quiz',
    questionText: 'What is the purpose of data analytics?',
    questionNumber: 5,
    weekNumber: 3,
    answers: [
      'To use data to make an image file',
      'To determine the sum of all values',
      'To use data for the purpose of analysis',
      'to analyze a news article',
    ],
    correctAnswer: 'To use data for the purpose of analysis',
  },
  {
    category: 'quiz',
    questionText:
      'Can a KPI (Key Performance Indicator) be used to define success?',
    questionNumber: 6,
    weekNumber: 3,
    answers: ['true', 'false'],
    correctAnswer: 'true',
  },
  {
    category: 'quiz',
    questionText: 'Which function is not an example of aggregation?',
    questionNumber: 7,
    weekNumber: 3,
    answers: ['SUM', 'MEDIAN', 'AVERAGE', 'REVERSE'],
    correctAnswer: 'REVERSE',
  },
  {
    category: 'quiz',
    questionText: 'Can Tableau calculate the p-value and r-squared values?',
    questionNumber: 8,
    weekNumber: 3,
    answers: ['true', 'false'],
    correctAnswer: 'true',
  },
  {
    category: 'quiz',
    questionText:
      'Which data visualization is most appropriate for data and time values?',
    questionNumber: 9,
    weekNumber: 3,
    answers: [
      'geographic map',
      'line chart',
      'multi-set column chart',
      'pie chart',
    ],
    correctAnswer: 'line chart',
  },
  {
    category: 'quiz',
    questionText:
      'Which visualization is best to show comparisons between two variables?',
    questionNumber: 10,
    weekNumber: 3,
    answers: ['line chart', 'scatter plot', 'heatmap', 'pie chart'],
    correctAnswer: 'scatter plot',
  },
  {
    category: 'quiz',
    questionText:
      'Can Tableau make use of the geographic coordinates system to visualize data?',
    questionNumber: 1,
    weekNumber: 4,
    answers: ['true', 'false'],
    correctAnswer: 'true',
  },
  {
    category: 'quiz',
    questionText:
      'Which example of a latitude value does Tableau recognize as a valid value?',
    questionNumber: 2,
    weekNumber: 4,
    answers: [
      '27.1721478',
      '15 degrees North',
      '77Â° 5\' 4.617" W',
      'Due South',
    ],
    correctAnswer: '27.1721478',
  },
  {
    category: 'quiz',
    questionText:
      'Tableau can display data on a map in greater detail than just the country level?',
    questionNumber: 3,
    weekNumber: 4,
    answers: ['true', 'false'],
    correctAnswer: 'true',
  },
  {
    category: 'quiz',
    questionText:
      'What are the advantages of using a geographic map to visualize data?',
    questionNumber: 4,
    weekNumber: 4,
    answers: [
      'maps facilitate data analysis in multiple dimensions',
      'maps are fun to use',
      'most data analysis is geographic-based',
      'Tableau can visualize maps best',
    ],
    correctAnswer: 'maps facilitate data analysis in multiple dimensions',
  },
  {
    category: 'quiz',
    questionText: 'Which geographic data part is not used in Tableau?',
    questionNumber: 5,
    weekNumber: 4,
    answers: ['City', 'Airport', 'Popular Landmark', 'Postal Code'],
    correctAnswer: 'Popular Landmark',
  },
  {
    category: 'quiz',
    questionText:
      'What is another name for a visualization that shows data on a map?',
    questionNumber: 6,
    weekNumber: 4,
    answers: ['scatter plot', 'bar chart', 'choropleth map', 'heatmap'],
    correctAnswer: 'choropleth map',
  },
  {
    category: 'quiz',
    questionText:
      'If Tableau does not display data on a map correctly, are there tools in Tableau to fix the problem?',
    questionNumber: 7,
    weekNumber: 4,
    answers: ['true', 'false'],
    correctAnswer: 'true',
  },
  {
    category: 'quiz',
    questionText:
      'In which geographic region would you use the NUTS (Nomenclature of Territorial Units for Statistics) standard?',
    questionNumber: 8,
    weekNumber: 4,
    answers: [
      'South America',
      'The GCC',
      'The Mid-Atlantic US States',
      'Europe',
    ],
    correctAnswer: 'Europe',
  },
  {
    category: 'quiz',
    questionText:
      'What data is needed to make use of the coordinate system in Tableau?',
    questionNumber: 9,
    weekNumber: 4,
    answers: [
      'longitude only',
      'latitude only',
      'both longitude and latitude',
      'population density',
    ],
    correctAnswer: 'both longitude and latitude',
  },
  {
    category: 'quiz',
    questionText:
      'Data used to create a geographic data visualizations in Tableau can only be used to create visualizations on a map?',
    questionNumber: 10,
    weekNumber: 4,
    answers: ['true', 'false'],
    correctAnswer: 'false',
  },
  {
    category: 'quiz',
    questionText: 'What is a good reason to choose to tell a story with data?',
    questionNumber: 1,
    weekNumber: 5,
    answers: [
      'Data can only be understood when told as a story',
      'Stories are more fun than a single chart',
      'The story teller can extract the meaningful information from the data',
      'People cannot understand complex data not presented as a story',
    ],
    correctAnswer:
      'The story teller can extract the meaningful information from the data',
  },
  {
    category: 'quiz',
    questionText: 'What definition best describes a data dashboard?',
    questionNumber: 2,
    weekNumber: 5,
    answers: [
      'it is a collection of separate data visualizations',
      'it is a way to show raw data',
      'it is a story telling tool',
      'it is a place to put as many visualizations as possible',
    ],
    correctAnswer: 'it is a collection of separate data visualizations',
  },
  {
    category: 'quiz',
    questionText:
      'Key Performance Indicators (KPI) can never be used in a data dashboard?',
    questionNumber: 3,
    weekNumber: 5,
    answers: ['true', 'false'],
    correctAnswer: 'false',
  },
  {
    category: 'quiz',
    questionText: 'What can be used to create a data story in Tableau',
    questionNumber: 4,
    weekNumber: 5,
    answers: [
      'individual visualizations',
      'data dashboards',
      'text and images',
      'all of the above',
    ],
    correctAnswer: 'all of the above',
  },
  {
    category: 'quiz',
    questionText: 'Can a data dashboard in Tableau be interactive?',
    questionNumber: 5,
    weekNumber: 5,
    answers: ['true', 'false'],
    correctAnswer: 'true',
  },
  {
    category: 'quiz',
    questionText: 'What is the best reason to use a data dashboard in Tableau?',
    questionNumber: 6,
    weekNumber: 5,
    answers: [
      'it is more fun for viewers',
      'it is more efficient than showing individual visualizations',
      'combining multiple related visualizations can help with analysis',
      'they are easy to build',
    ],
    correctAnswer:
      'combining multiple related visualizations can help with analysis',
  },
  {
    category: 'quiz',
    questionText:
      'Can controls to change the display of a visualization be placed on a data dashboard?',
    questionNumber: 7,
    weekNumber: 5,
    answers: ['true', 'false'],
    correctAnswer: 'true',
  },
  {
    category: 'quiz',
    questionText:
      'Which of the following is an object that can be added to a data dashboard?',
    questionNumber: 8,
    weekNumber: 5,
    answers: ['website', 'image', 'text', 'all of the above'],
    correctAnswer: 'all of the above',
  },
  {
    category: 'quiz',
    questionText:
      'Can one data visualization be used to filter another data visualizations on a data dashboard?',
    questionNumber: 9,
    weekNumber: 5,
    answers: ['true', 'false'],
    correctAnswer: 'true',
  },
  {
    category: 'quiz',
    questionText:
      'What is the best way to control the order of visualizations in a Tableau Story?',
    questionNumber: 10,
    weekNumber: 5,
    answers: [
      'enabling website navigation',
      'using story points',
      'turning on auto advance',
      'all of the above',
    ],
    correctAnswer: 'using story points',
  },
];
